嗯  我也想你了  亲爱的
Yeah, I miss you, too, sweetie.
我得挂了  晚上见吧
Listen, I got to go, but I'll see you tonight?
好的 拜拜 拜拜
Okay. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
不  你先挂嘛
No, you hang up first.
喂
Hello?
老兄  我为你好不容易找到个女朋友而高兴
Dude, I'm glad you finally got a girlfriend,
但你非得当着我们这些光棍的面
but do you have to do all that lovey-dovey stuff
玩那套你亲我热的把戏吗
in front of those of us who don't?
事实上  他也许该当如此
Actually, he might have to.
在经济学里有种概念被称之为地位商品
There's an economic concept known as a positional good
它只在持有人手中才能彰显其价值
in which an object is only valued by the possessor
因为其他人无法拥有
because it's not possessed by others.
这个词由经济学家弗列得·赫希杜撰于1976年
The term was coined in 1976 by economist Fred Hirsch
用来取代更口语化  但并不准确的"哦也-哦也"[嘲讽]
to replace the more colloquial, but less precise "neener-neener."
才不是呢
That's not true.
我的快乐不是建立于
My happiness is not dependent
挚友的杯具与孤独之上的
on my best friend being miserable and alone.
谢谢
Thank you.
当然  要说我没得儿意地笑肯定是说谎了
Although, I'd be lying if I said it wasn't a little bit of a perk.
谁杯具和孤独了
Who's miserable and alone?
我
Me.
我以前也这样 直到我有了女朋友
I used to be like that. Then I got a girlfriend.
用1976年之前的话来说  "哦也-哦也"
In pre-1976 terms, neener-neener.
嘿  你和伯纳黛特准备如何 共度你们的第一个情人节
Hey, what are you and Bernadette doing for your first Valentine's Day?
啊  我可是绞尽脑汁了
Yeah, I am pulling out all the stops.
华馆提供了39.95美金的情侣特典套餐
There's a $39.95 lover's special at P.F. Chang's.
蛋卷啊  饺子啊
Egg rolls, dumplings,
数不清的炒菜  最后你还能和门口硕大的
bottomless wok, and you get your picture taken
大理石马合影留念
on the big marble horse out front.
考虑到圣瓦伦丁是个在公元三世纪
Given that Saint Valentine was a third century Roman priest
被丢石头和斩首的罗马祭司
who was stoned and beheaded,
在这个夜晚带着女朋友去看一场残忍的凶杀
wouldn't a more appropriate celebration of the evening
难道不是更合情理的庆祝方式吗
be taking one's steady gal to witness a brutal murder?
我明白你的意思  但是有选择的话
I understand your point, but given a choice,
犹太人永远选择中国菜
Jews always go with Chinese food.
呃  如果任何人有兴趣
Well, if anyone's interested,
今年的情人节
I'll be spending this Valentine's Day
我会像往年一样
the same way I spend every Valentine's Day.
从超市买只大烤鸡
Buying a rotisserie chicken from the supermarket,
带回家  站在洗手池边
taking it home, standing over the sink
像只禽兽一样直接打开包装用手抓着吃
and eating it out of the package with my bare hands like an animal.
很好  那总结一下  一个是大理石骏马
Okay, so to sum up: one giant marble horse,
一条愚蠢之极的意见 剩男则独自回家吃鸡
one asinine comment, one lonely man and his chicken.
让我们看看  还剩谁呢
And let's see. Who's left?
没错  就剩我的计划了
Oh, that's right. My plans.
有人想要问一下吗
Isn't anyone going to ask?
好吧  告诉我们你会和佩妮云雨一番
Fine, tell us you're going to have sex with Penny.
这不是我想说的
That's not what I was going to tell you.
没关系 我不介意听听你的性生活
It's okay. I don't mind hearing about your sex life.
只有他的才会让我抓狂
It's his that bugs me.
你们猜学校要派谁去瑞士
Guess who the university is sending to Switzerland
参加研讨会并参观欧洲核子研究委员会的超级对撞机
to attend a conference and see the CERN supercollider
就在二月十四日
on February 14?
诺顿教授  尽管原因只有上帝才知道
Professor Norton, although, God knows why.
他自从获得诺贝尔奖之后
He hasn't published anything of note
就再也没有发表过任何著名的文章
since he won that Nobel Prize.
事实上  诺顿教授去不成了
Actually, Professor Norton can't make it.
他在攀岩的时候把腰扭了
He threw his back out rock climbing.
我怎么听说他是在攀新女友的高峰时把腰扭了
I heard he threw his back out climbing on his new girlfriend.
就是第二台的那个爆乳天气女郎吗
The big-boobed weather girl on Channel 2?
就是她
That's the one.
不管怎样  他们邀请我代替他
In any case, they're asking me to fill in for him.
是瑞士还是爆乳天气女郎
In Switzerland or with the big-boobed weather girl?
瑞士
Switzerland.
而且我还能带一个人去
And I get to bring a guest!
哦  天呐  不可能  老兄
Oh, man! No way, dude!
太难以置信了
This is incredible!
我太开心了
I'm so happy,
我甚至不想去质疑他们为什么会选你去了
I'm not even going to question their judgment in picking you.
我要速度奔回家收拾行李
I'm just going to run home and start packing.
你怎么不带佩妮去
Why wouldn't you take Penny?
我是要带佩妮去的
I am taking Penny.
那我预测你回家会面临个尴尬的境地
Well, then I anticipate an awkward situation when you get home.
生活大爆炸
第三季第十五集
谢尔顿  有空吗
Sheldon, you got a minute?
当然了  我的好朋友
Of course, my good friend.
请进
Come in.
帮我参考一下
Help me out.
哪顶滑雪帽比较像超级对撞机
Which ski hat says aprey supercollider?
谢尔顿  我没有选你去瑞士
Sheldon, I'm not taking you to Switzerland.
你当然选我了
Well, of course you are.
你还能选谁呢
Who else would you take?
佩妮
Penny.
什么 这太荒谬了
What? That's absurd.
佩妮对亚原子粒子的研究又不感兴趣
Penny has no interest in subatomic particle research.
没错  但那是情人节啊
Yes, but it'll be Valentine's Day.
我们可以去观光滑雪
We can go sightseeing and skiing
然后在熊熊炉火前与皑皑白雪所覆盖的
and make love in front of a roaring fire
阿尔卑斯山阴中共度春宵
in the shadow of the snowcapped Alps.
但佩妮对亚原子粒子的研究不感兴趣啊
But Penny has no interest in subatomic particle research.
抱歉  谢尔顿
I'm sorry, Sheldon.
抱歉
Sorry?
我自从九岁起就一直梦想着有朝一日
I've been dreaming about going to the Large Hadron Collider
去看大型强子对撞机
since I was nine years old.
是吗  那我还从六岁起就梦想有朝一日有个女生
Yeah, well, I've been dreaming about spending Valentine's Day
能与我共度情人节呢
with a girl since I was six.
太可耻了
Shame on you!
这不是科学家该有的梦
That's no dream for a scientist!
你要给我什么巨大的惊喜啊
Okay, what's the big surprise?
稍等一下
Just a minute.
这个托盘里藏着
This tray contains clues
你和我如何共度情人节的线索
as to what you and I are going to be doing on Valentine's Day.
喔  好吧
Oh. Wow. Okay.
让我看看
Let's see.
有牛奶巧克力
We've got, uh, milk chocolate,
瑞士硬干酪  芝士火锅
Swiss cheese, fondue.
我的乳糖不耐症男友要吃完这些
My lactose-intolerant boyfriend is going to eat all this.
然后我骑在他背上 直冲月球
Then I'm going to climb on his back and rocket to the moon?
不对
No.
但的确跟空中旅行有关
But it does involve air travel.
这样吧
Okay, um...
我用"瑞士"军刀 切一片"瑞士"干酪
let me slice this Swiss cheese with my Swiss army knife,
你可以把它加到一杯 "瑞士"小姐速溶可可里
and then you can wash it down with a cup of Swiss Miss instant cocoa.
嗯  我觉得瑞士应该是个关键词了
Okay, I'm starting to think Swiss is key here.
没错
Uh-huh.
去迪士尼乐园玩马特洪峰雪橇过山车
We're going to Disneyland and ride the Matterhorn?
这怎么会跟空中旅行有关
How does that involve air travel?
去迪士尼世界玩马特洪雪橇过山车[奥兰多  佛罗里达]
We're going to Disney World and ride the Matterhorn?
不对
No.
亲爱的  开始是挺好玩的 但现在没意思了
Okay, sweetie, this started out fun, but I'm over it.
我们要去瑞士的
We're going to Switzerland
欧洲核子研究中心参观超级对撞机
to see the CERN supercollider!
还有去滑雪
And ski. We'll also go skiing.
我们要去瑞士滑雪
We're going skiing in Switzerland?!
你滑  我会摔倒  不过是的
Well, you'll ski, I'll fall, but, yeah,
我们要去瑞士过情人节
we will be in Switzerland for Valentine's Day.
天啊  莱纳德 太好了
Oh, my God, Leonard! That's incredible!
别高兴得太早
Not so fast.
先别急着点 你的芜菁灯吧  佩妮
You might want to hold off on lighting your rabeliechtli, Penny.
芜什么玩意儿
Rabe-what-ly?
芜菁灯 芜菁灯
Rabeliechtli. It means turnip light
是一种用根菜 手工雕刻的传统灯笼
and refers to a traditional lantern hand-carved from a root vegetable
用于庆祝瑞士的特定节日
and used to celebrate certain Swiss festivals.
但你不会参加
Which you will not be celebrating
原因之一  节日在秋季
because A: these festivals occur in the fall;
原因之二
and B:
你去不了瑞士
you will not be going to Switzerland.
谢尔顿  我们谈过了
Sheldon, we've been through this.
我带佩妮去
I'm taking Penny.
估计不行 你还认得这个吗
Afraid not. Do you recognize this?
别提室友协议
Not the roommate agreement.
正是室友协议
Indeed, the roommate agreement.
请您注意友谊附加条款
I call your attention to the Friendship Rider
在附录C  未来义务
in Appendix C: Future Commitments.
第37条  当一位朋友受邀
"Number 37: in the event one friend is ever invited
参观现在瑞士建设中的
"to visit the Large Hadron Collider,
大型强子对撞机
"now under construction in Switzerland,
该人应邀请另一位朋友相陪
he shall invite the other friend to accompany him."
偶滴神啊
Oh, for God's sakes.
你们连这个也写进协议里吗
You actually put that in an agreement?
里面还写了
Yeah. We also put in what happens
如果一人得了麦克阿瑟天才奖怎么办
if one of us wins a MacArthur Grant,
如果一人有超能力怎么办
or if one of us gets superpowers,
如果一人被僵尸咬了怎么办
or if one of us is bitten by a zombie.
就算我尸变  他也不能杀我
He can't kill me, even if I turn.
里面没写一人有了女友怎么办吗
Is there anything in there about if one of you gets a girlfriend?
没有  那个有点太不着调了
No, that seemed a little farfetched.
谢尔顿  你真打算强制实施这个吗
Sheldon, do you really expect to enforce this?
我一直遵守
I've lived up
协议里的所有义务
to all my commitments under the agreement.
每天至少问候你一次
At least once a day I ask how you are,
即使我一点都不在意
even though I simply don't care.
我没有
I no longer
在晚上十点后进行生物危害演习了
stage spontaneous biohazard drills after 10:00 p.m.
我也放弃学习图瓦喉唱了
And I abandoned my goal to master Tuvan throat singing.
-我知道不该问  不过什么是  -别啊
- Okay, I know I shouldn't ask, but what is...? - No.
如果允许我训练  我能唱得更好
I'd be much further along if I'd been allowed to practice.
谢尔顿 我知道协议这么写
Look, Sheldon, i know it's in the agreement,
如果你真的变成僵尸  我保证不杀你
and if you turn into a zombie, I promise I will not kill you.
我宁愿让你喝我脑浆
In fact, I'll even let you eat my brains.
但我还是要带佩妮去瑞士
But I am taking Penny to Switzerland.
这是你的最终决定吗
Is that your final decision?
没错
It is.
很好
Very well.
他不会罢休  对吧
It's not over, is it?
你以为呢
What do you think?
今早的车挺多啊
Got a bit of traffic this morning, huh?
你觉得会下雨吗
Think it's gonna rain?
今天早上
Instead of underpants,
我把土豆沙拉当内裤穿了
I covered my crotch with potato salad this morning.
有啥想法
Thoughts?
我知道怎么让你高兴
Okay, I know what'll cheer you up.
我们玩你的开车游戏吧
Let's play one of your driving games.
好啊
All right.
游戏名就叫叛徒
This game is called Traitors.
我说三个历史人物
I will name three historical figures,
你以背叛行为的罪恶程度
you put them in order
来给他们排下序
of the heinousness of their betrayal.
本尼迪克特·阿诺德  犹大  莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德博士
Benedict Arnold, Judas, Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.
你真觉得我跟他们是一类人吗
You really think I belong with Benedict Arnold and Judas?
你说得对
You're right.
犹大至少为自己的作为 以死谢罪了
Judas had the decency to hang himself after what he did.
别这样  谢尔顿 你就不能理解一下
Come on, Sheldon. Can't you at least try to understand
这对我有多重要吗
how much this means to me?
第二轮  莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德
Round two: Leonard Hofstadter,
达斯·维达[星战黑武士]  鲁珀特·默多克
Darth Vader, Rupert Murdoch.
鲁珀特·默多克
Rupert Murdoch?
福克斯电视台老板  他们把《萤火虫》砍了
He owns Fox, and they cancelled Firefly.
提示  他和达斯·维达并列第二
Hint: he and Darth Vader are tied for #2.
对不起昨晚不能陪你
I'm sorry I couldn't hang with you last night.
我和伯纳黛特约会了
I had a date with Bernadette.
我知道
I know.
我在推特上看到了
I saw the Tweet.
那你干什么了
So, what did you end up doing?
没干什么
Not much.
热了块玉米馅饼
Nuked a burrito. Oh.
向印度女神乌尔瓦希祈祷你会拉稀
Prayed to the Hindu god Urvashi that your bowels would loosen
老二蔫得跟柳条一样柔软
and your penis would droop like a willow tree.
看到谢尔顿了吗
You seen Sheldon?
没有  他还在为超级对撞机的事生气吗
No. Is he still mad about the supercollider?
对  他觉得我背叛了他
Yeah. He thinks I betrayed him.
搞什么啊 要是你们会带谁
I mean, come on. What would you guys do if you were me?
我会带谢尔顿去瑞士
I'd take Sheldon to Switzerland.
真的假的
Seriously?
当然了
Absolutely.
再把他扔在那里
And I'd leave him there.
这是什么情况
What the hell is that?
让我数数
Uh, let's see.
30把银制餐具
30 pieces of silverware.
[格里格  培尔金特组曲之晨曦]
Grieg "Peer Gynt - Morning"
早安  老伙计
Morning, old chum.
搞什么
What's going on?
我给你做了早餐
I've made you breakfast.
有果汁和咖啡
Juice, coffee,
还有一些薄饼
and pancakes in the shape of some
上面是你最爱的虚构角色
of your favorite fictional characters.
瞧  这是弗罗多[出自《魔戒》]
See, here's Frodo.
你居然做了弗罗多薄饼
You made Frodo pancakes?
脚毛部分我用的是椰子刨花
Yeah, I used coconut shavings to do the hair on his feet.
你进餐前若需要清空膀胱
If you need to void your bladder before eating,
我会用这顶贝雷帽帮你暖着
I can keep them warm with this beret
我已经彻底清洗干净
that I thoroughly laundered
松软程度正适宜用来盖薄饼
and pressed into service as a pancake cozy.
你有什么目的
Why are you doing this?
对我近来的行为表示歉意
It's by way of an apology for my recent behavior.
经过这段时间的思考 我终于意识到
I've had some time to reflect and I've come to realize
友谊不能依靠那堆 白纸黑字的协定来维系
that friendship is not an aggregation of written agreements.
而需要两人之间 互相尊重和体谅
It's a result of two people respecting and caring for each other.
尝尝奶油烤饼吗
Butterscotch scone?
多谢
Thanks.
好吃
It's good.
这其中包含着我满满的尊敬和感情
What you're tasting is respect and affection.
当然还有一磅左右植物白油
And about a pound of Crisco.
待你用完早餐 我觉得  今天我们可以
After you've finished breakfast, i thought we could spend the day
一起看导演点评版的 巴比伦5号[美国科幻剧]
watching the final season of Babylon 5 with director commentary.
你不是讨厌《巴比伦5号》吗
You hate Babylon 5.
当然  既没剧情又不科幻
I do. It fails as drama/science fiction,
彻头彻尾的仿制大烂片
and it's hopelessly derivative.
但是你喜欢  而我们又是朋友
But you like it, and you're my friend.
好吧  赞
Okay, great.
我还是不会带你去瑞士
Still not taking you to Switzerland.
见鬼
Drat.
没你的弗罗多尝了
No Frodo for you.
你好
Hello.
好啊
得  我们就省掉假惺惺的友好吧
All right, let's dispense with the friendly banter.
你应该知道我为何来此
I believe you know why I'm here.
关于这点  我一直认为
Well, I always figured it was to study us,
你是来发现我们地球人的弱点
discover our weaknesses,
再报告给你们的外星君主
and report back to your alien overlords.
搞笑
Yes, amusing.
特定情报  对你而言
Extraordinary intelligence
貌似是显得像天外来客般难懂
might well appear extraterrestrial to you,
但我还是友情提醒下 确切地说
but let me be more specific.
你应该知道我为何在此  这个洗衣间里
I believe you know why I'm here in the laundry room.
喉音唱腔在这里有更好的音响效果吗
Better acoustics for your throat singing?
还真不赖嘛
It's actually not bad.
但我来此的真正目的
But my true purpose in being here
是来做一个简要的幻灯片演说
will be revealed in this brief PowerPoint presentation.
关灯
Lights.
为什么谢尔顿·库珀博士必须去瑞士欧核中心
Why Sheldon Cooper, PhD, should go to Switzerland
参观超级对撞机的理由
to see the CERN supercollider:
发言人  谢尔顿·库珀博士
a PowerPoint presentation by Sheldon Cooper, PhD.
我的老天爷
Oh, for God's sake.
这是一位在粒子物理学领域的
Here we have a highly gifted researcher
超级天才科学家
in the field of particle physics
他的成就关乎全人类的命运
whose work has brought him to the precipice
从此改变对宇宙的理解
of forever changing mankind's understanding of the universe.
确切来说就是我
AKA me.
而这是一位女招待
And here we have a waitress
只会用手指抠牙齿而已
brushing her teeth with her finger.
确切来说就是你
AKA you.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
这算是在奉承我吗
Is this supposed to be buttering me up?
请等演讲结束后再提问
Please hold all questions till the end of the presentation.
这是瑞士欧核中心的
This is the Large Hadron Collider
大型强子对撞机
at CERN in Switzerland,
经由数十年规划和建构而成
the product of decades of planning and construction.
是全世界物理学家心目中的圣地
It is a Mecca for physicists the world over.
而这是科罗拉多大街的
This is Bath and Body Works
Bath and Body Works[某品牌]沐浴乳商店
on Colorado Boulevard.
他们卖香皂和乳液
They sell scented soaps and lotions,
外加一些小闪饰品
some of which contain glitter.
现在我们来配对
Now, let's see if we can match the individual
这两个人以哪个地方作为目的地比较合适
to the appropriate destination.
好吧
O-kay.
别闹了
Show's over.
还没完呢
No, it's not.
我还有五张幻灯片没讲
I've got five more slides.
谢尔顿  这是莱纳德的决定
Sheldon, this is Leonard's decision.
他邀我去瑞士  我也很想去
He invited me to Switzerland, and I intend to go.
好吧
Very well.
玩得开心
Enjoy yourself.
你将亲眼目睹
You're going to be in the presence of something
我所梦寐以求了十多年的伟大成就
that I've dreamed of seeing for decades.
希望你能明白
I just hope you'll be able to appreciate
这其中所包含的重要意义
the magnitude of where you are and what it represents.
我会和莱纳德谈谈
I'll talk to Leonard.
真的吗
You will?
对
Yes.
既然对你而言意义重大  那应该让你去
If it means that much to you, you should go.
谢谢你  佩妮
Oh, Penny, thank you!
没什么
You're welcome.
我不怎么抱人
Since I rarely hug,
要抱多久就听你的
I'm relying on your expertise regarding duration.
我觉得差不多了
I think we're there.
好极了
Oh, good.
拜啦
Bye-bye.
你猜怎么着
You know what?
没有马子又怎样
Even though I don't have a girlfriend,
情人节老子照样可以好好过
I can still have a good time on Valentine's Day.
听我的吧  这不可能 我早试过了
Trust me, you can't. I've tried.
不  我准备好好过我自己的情人节
No, no, no, I'm going to have a "me" day.
首先  去韩国城找家店做个SPA
First I'm going to go to one of those SPAs in Koreatown,
蒸个桑拿  找人按摩一下
take a steam and get a massage.
然后去宠物店  找条小狗狗来舔舔我
Then I'm going to stop at a pet store and get licked by puppies.
谢尔顿 我得跟你谈谈
Sheldon, I need to talk to you.
好的  朋友 来点Cholermus煎饼尝尝吗
All right, my friend. Would you like some Cholermus?
尝什么
Some what?
Cholermus煎饼 一种传统的瑞士早餐
Cholermus. It's a traditional Swiss breakfast dish.
我正在训练我的消化系统
I'm preparing my gastrointestinal system
习惯瑞士菜特殊的烹饪方法
for the exotic cuisine of Switzerland.
又轮不上你去瑞士
You're not going to Switzerland!
但我要去
Oh, but I am.
佩妮没告诉你最新的好消息吗
Didn't Penny tell you the good news?
她跟我说  你背着我去找她
She told me that you went behind my back
让她觉得内疚  主动提出让你替代她去瑞士
to guilt her into letting you go instead of her.
对  就是这个好消息
Yes, that good news.
想都别想  我才是受邀的人
Well, forget it. I was the one who was invited.
只有我能决定找谁同行
I get to decide who goes with me,
我决定找佩妮  而不是你
and it's Penny, not you!
霍华德  把灯光调暗点好吗
Howard, could you lower the lights?
我做了段简短的幻灯片演示文稿
I have a short PowerPoint presentation.
没必要看什么演示
I don't need to see your presentation.
讨论到此为止了
This discussion is over!
这回答有够模棱两可的
That's a somewhat ambiguous response.
到底带不带我去
Am I going or not?
谢尔顿  事已至此
Sheldon, at this point,
我宁愿自己去  也不带你
I would go by myself before I would take you.
真的
Really?
Yeah, really.
好吧  那我也别无选择了
Well, then, you leave me no alternative.
从现在起
From this moment forward,
我们可以当室友  但不再是朋友了
we can be roommates, but we will no longer be friends.
很遗憾你这么觉得
I'm sorry you feel that way.
我认为你还未充分意识到
I don't think you're fully aware
此事的后果  莱纳德
of the ramifications here, Leonard.
你何不指点一下
Why don't you enlighten me?
既然我们"室友协议"中的友谊条款无效了
With the friendship clause of our Roommate Agreement nullified
等我受邀去比尔·盖茨家游泳的时候
you are no longer entitled to accompany me
你也就失去了随同一起去的资格
to go swimming at Bill Gates' house should I be invited.
那可伤大了
Ooh, that's gotta sting.
想想看  明天这个时候
Just think, this time tomorrow
我们已经在瑞士日内瓦 共度我俩第一个情人节了
we'll be in Geneva, Switzerland for our first Valentine's Day.
是啊
I know!
我今天特地去逛街
I went shopping today
专门为此行买了件小内内呢
and bought special undies for the occasion.
保暖吗  那边会很冷哦
Thermal?'Cause it's gonna be cold.
再好好想想  莱纳德
Think it through, Leonard.
祝你健康[用于对刚打喷嚏者的祝愿]
Gesundheit.
或者学他们瑞士人讲话
Or as they say in Switzerland,
祝您健康
Gesundheit.
你感冒了吗
You getting a cold?
不  可能只是有点过敏
No, no, it's probably just allergies.
想吃点抗过敏药吗
Do you want an allergy pill?
我啥都有哦
'Cause I have 'em all.
处方药  非处方药
Prescription, nonprescription,
进口药  国产药  实验性药物
foreign, domestic, experimental.
有管用的吗
Do any of them work?
没  我只是喜欢收集
Not really, I'm just an enthusiast.
佩妮
Penny?
你还好吧
You okay?
我听起来很好的样子吗
Did that sound okay to you?
别进来
Do not come in here!
怎么回事
What's going on?
我这儿开茶话会呢
I'm having a tea party.
不然你以为怎么回事
What do you think's going on?
我想我可能得了流感
I think I might have the flu.
要不就是瘟疫
Or the plague.
我们是早上9点的飞机
Well, our plane leaves at 9:00 a.m.
你觉得到那时你会感觉好点吗
Do you think you'll feel better by then?
会的
Yep.
因为那时我早已痛苦至死了
'Cause I'm gonna be dead.
谢尔顿
Hey, Sheldon?
佩妮病得很重
Listen, Penny is pretty sick
不能去瑞士了
and she's not going to be able to go to Switzerland.
你还有兴趣的话  欢迎随我一起去
So if you're still interested, you're welcome to come.
太好了
Great.
我这就去收拾行李
I'll start packing.
等我一下
In a minute.
Cholermus煎饼都吐出来了
Oh, look, it's the Cholermus.
你的汤
Here's your soup.
-鸡汤  -对
- Chicken? - Yes.
-加了点小点缀的  -对
- With the little stars? - Yes.
加热到180度
Heated to 180 degrees?
不如我倒你膝盖上  你来告诉我到底几度
Why don't I pour it in your lap and you can tell me?
不必这么刻薄吧
You don't have to be mean.
我是病人
I'm sick.
是啊  我也是病人
Yeah, well, I'm sick, too.
不关我事
Not my problem.
我就是想不明白  我怎么会生病的
I just don't understand how this happened to me.
我对个人卫生一向一丝不苟
I'm scrupulous about my hygiene.
还定期给双手消毒
I regularly disinfect my hands,
一般来说  还都避免接触到别人
and I avoid contact with other people on general principle.
我不知道怎么说  谢尔顿
I don't know what to tell you, Sheldon.
佩妮  谢谢你
Oh, Penny, thank you!
不客气
You're welcome.
是你
It's you!
我拥抱过你
I touched you!
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day.
天哪  看看这房间
Oh, my goodness, look at this room!
香槟
Champagne!
玫瑰
Roses!
还有巧克力
And little chocolates!
这一定是我有生以来最棒的情人节
This is going to be the best Valentine's Day ever.
对了  我忘了还准备了这些
Yeah, I forgot about all this.
但我可永世难忘
But I never will.